<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title></title>
        <link>undefined</link>
        <description>undefined</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 18:07:26 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>Joplin Pages Publisher</generator>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Baby AJ]]></title>
            <guid>ba44549bbeeb438d9329bf03ec531696</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 07:15:48 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="/_resources/654f502ef6d142cbab633dcb3e738d9e.JPG" />]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A tired dog is a happy dog]]></title>
            <guid>59924eee4ea6427b950e7a1d9b2ad1cc</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 20:15:16 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>"A tired dog is a happy dog" is a saying of mine.<br />
I think I made it up<br />
But in any case it's true.</p>
<p>And it's true of boys I think as well. It's something boys and dogs have in common.</p>
<p>And that's something I told my kids, my daughters, is that it's probably best to assume that a boy is like a dog.</p>
<p>He wants to please but he's not that bright.  he can't read your mind and most of the time he's just confused.</p>
<p>Haha.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[old sol’s last light ]]></title>
            <guid>0b90b42e0e224b60af4c5986094b2a14</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 14:36:02 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Last night I watched the sun go down<br />
And as old sol’s last light became squished and flattened and finally nothing more than a bright yellow dot disappearing behind the horizon I was overcome with a sense of loss and I was reminded of Anita's passing and I longed to have it — the sun — back and to have her —  Anita — back with me again</p>
<p>Those days of our youth seemed like the day and these days seem like the night.</p>
<p>The cold, dark, lonely night.</p>
<p>Sometimes it’s unbearable.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[some things are todos, ...]]></title>
            <guid>f54ae04058e742d1ae20ae813c494166</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2015 16:33:01 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[some things are todos, and some things are howtos, and some things are rants, some are can'ts and some are won'ts. sometimes things are dos and sometimes they are don'ts. sometimes things just don't look right to you, and if you're feeling it, you can bet someone else is feeling it too. I'm gonna tell you how its gonna be, I won't be that way to you, and you don't be that way to me. just one thing I gotta say, .. hey, ok?]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>