<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title></title>
        <link>undefined</link>
        <description>undefined</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 18:22:10 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>Joplin Pages Publisher</generator>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Baby AJ]]></title>
            <guid>ba44549bbeeb438d9329bf03ec531696</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 07:15:48 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<img src="/_resources/654f502ef6d142cbab633dcb3e738d9e.JPG" />]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[I took it in my mind]]></title>
            <guid>3ff35b975f614e7890135e7774dd5932</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 20:31:10 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I took it in my mind</p>
<p>I took it in my mind to read something I wrote about this shit</p>
<p>You know you’re born and you have no idea what you’re getting into<br />
And then you grow up a little and think maybe you’re starting to get a handle on it<br />
But nope you’re wrong.</p>
<p>And then life really kicks you in the gut and you think this is it.<br />
this is really it.<br />
This is reality and it sucks and it’s depressing and there is no bottom</p>
<p>but you’re still wrong and you’ll never figure it out because it’s too big and too obvious and it's right next to you.</p>
<p>It’s all around you.  Life is all around you, love is all around you.</p>
<p>but death is all around you too.<br />
it’s the other side of life<br />
the other half.<br />
the opposite which defines the other.<br />
It's the shadow that defines the light, and makes the thing apparent to the human mind.</p>
<p>And the knowledge of death has a generative power, it's mysterious, eternal and universal.<br />
It makes you cherish the brief life you do have, the love we share, how rare and precious it all is.</p>
<p>These are the kind of things Rob and I used to talk about.<br />
But nevermind any of that.</p>
<p>what I want to say is that I always felt very close to you Rob, from the  time you were a little kid playing with your sisters and your cousins.</p>
<p>you couldn't have been happier.  I know because I have been there myself, and you brought me back, you brought me there again, we were all there together.</p>
<p>And over the years as you grew up, we recognized each other.</p>
<p>you were one of us.</p>
<p>we were mostly separated in space and time.  but I can say that I felt as close to you as I have ever felt to anyone.</p>
<p>I still do feel close to you, Rob.  I loved you and I love you still.</p>
<p>but the worst part is that I know you loved me too and now that love has passed from the world and I am the lesser for it as are we all.</p>
<p>But the world is a better place because you were in it Rob, even if only for a little while.</p>
<p>Love you forever!</p>
<p>Ps. 103:15<br />
Eccl. 5:2</p>
]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A tired dog is a happy dog]]></title>
            <guid>59924eee4ea6427b950e7a1d9b2ad1cc</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 20:15:16 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>"A tired dog is a happy dog" is a saying of mine.<br />
I think I made it up<br />
But in any case it's true.</p>
<p>And it's true of boys I think as well. It's something boys and dogs have in common.</p>
<p>And that's something I told my kids, my daughters, is that it's probably best to assume that a boy is like a dog.</p>
<p>He wants to please but he's not that bright.  he can't read your mind and most of the time he's just confused.</p>
<p>Haha.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[old sol’s last light ]]></title>
            <guid>0b90b42e0e224b60af4c5986094b2a14</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 14:36:02 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Last night I watched the sun go down<br />
And as old sol’s last light became squished and flattened and finally nothing more than a bright yellow dot disappearing behind the horizon I was overcome with a sense of loss and I was reminded of Anita's passing and I longed to have it — the sun — back and to have her —  Anita — back with me again</p>
<p>Those days of our youth seemed like the day and these days seem like the night.</p>
<p>The cold, dark, lonely night.</p>
<p>Sometimes it’s unbearable.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[some things are todos, ...]]></title>
            <guid>f54ae04058e742d1ae20ae813c494166</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2015 16:33:01 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[some things are todos, and some things are howtos, and some things are rants, some are can'ts and some are won'ts. sometimes things are dos and sometimes they are don'ts. sometimes things just don't look right to you, and if you're feeling it, you can bet someone else is feeling it too. I'm gonna tell you how its gonna be, I won't be that way to you, and you don't be that way to me. just one thing I gotta say, .. hey, ok?]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>